W-wait, please!
I'm Liliel's photographer!
I just want to talk!
Would that be okay?
Together With You
I can hold it for you if you want.
He's the guy from the store!
Thank goodness.
RUMBLE
What did you want to talk about?
PANIC PANIC
Sorry!
Suddenly getting approached by some
random guy probably freaked you out!
I'm not really good at talking to new people.
I had to work up the courage to catch you.
Other people need to work up the
courage to talk to people, too?
I wanted to ask you a question.
I want to believe all cosplayers are friends and allies.
H-how do you feel about Liliel?
I love her! I love her so much!
I want to be her friend!
So, uh...
I'm guessing you don't like her.
No!
When that ranking came out,
I was kind of annoyed about it.
Like, my Liliel deserves to be number one.
I'm sorry I ranked higher!
She's way more adorable than me!
I know cosplay's not a competition,
and the ranking doesn't matter.
I should just be happy that Liliel's having fun.
But I still feel weird about it,
and I don't know what to do.
Do you feel the same way?
Were you annoyed to get fourth?
If you think Liliel's your
rival and aren't a fan of her,
could you tell me why you feel that way?
I think it'd help me figure out how to feel, too.
He's taking this so seriously.
But oh, god, he's got it all wrong!
It's okay if you don't like her.
Real otaku don't judge someone
for what they like or don't like.
They don't judge...
Some cosplayers want to try
and be better than other cosplayers,
and that's totally fine.
If that's why you don't like Liliel,
I'm totally okay with that.
I just want to understand.
He wants to understand?
He wants to know what I'm thinking?
He's taking this so seriously...
It's kind of weird.
Yet I don't feel uncomfortable.
I feel like he'd listen to what I have to say.
But... I'm sorry.
I can't get my voice to work.
If you talking is hard for you, I can wait.
Wait?
If I'm not bothering you, I guess.
I'll even turn the other way.
How long have we been here?
Five, ten minutes?
He's seriously going to wait?
I'm breathing calmly again.
I...
Yes?
I wanted to thank you... for helping me.
I spoke!
He didn't want me to say that!
I'm being weird again!
Sure, no problem!
He... responded to me.
Over here!
Smile!
Does Nonoa-chan really hate me?
Then if she had fans here,
would they hate me too?
Wouldn't they hate me for bringing
Liliel to a Cinderella Stars event?!
The more I think,
the more I feel like everyone hates me!
Sorry, I need to take a break!
I'm sorry, Sensei.
You okay? You're totally out of it today.
Liliel!
Nagomi-san?!
What's wrong with you?!
You don't look like you're enjoying this at all!
Did I put too much pressure on you?
No, you didn't put any pressure on me at all.
At least feel a little, sheesh.
You're worried about Nonoa,
and if she likes you or not.
Why're you so worked up about that?
Who cares if someone doesn't like you.
Don't look at me! I've moved on from that.
Look, Liliel...
I know I just figured this out,
so I'm the last person who
should be lecturing you, but...
I love all cosplayers.
But that doesn't mean that
everyone has to like me, too.
Everyone's entitled to their own opinions.
As much as I want everyone to like me,
I can't control how they feel about me.
I don't have psychic powers.
I can't move rocks with my mind,
or manpiulate someone's thoughts.
So if someone doesn't like me,
I should just accept it?
No.
I'm saying you shouldn't waste your time
wondering if someone likes you or not.
It doesn't matter what other people think.
What matters is what you think.
That's the only thing that should matter to you.
What do you think of her, Liliel?
If you don't like her,
you don't have to be her friend.
Just ignore her.
You're entitled to your opinion, too.
I...
I want to be her friend.
I mean, cosplayers all love the same thing!
We're all on the same team!
I totally agree.
So go get her!
If you tell her how you feel,
you might just change the
way she feels about you.
Right! Thank you!
I said something.
I finally told someone how I feel.
And now...
I have to tell her, too!
She probably hates me,
but I don't want this misunderstanding
to go on any longer!
RRRRUMBLE
I won't even ask to be friends.
I just need a chance to tell her how I feel.
I love you.
I have to make sure Liliel-chan hears that!
Nonoa-chan!
Liliel-chan!
It's okay if she hates me.
I love her.
I need her to know!
Sensei!
Okumura, where have you been?
Where's Ririsa?
She went to go look for Nonoa.
I'm sure she's not a bad person.
She's just a little awkward.
Ririsa will understand!
Nonoa-chan!
C-can we get some pictures of you?
We've been looking for you!
I'm sorry, I'm in a hurry!
I-is that a no?
No, Nonoa-chan doesn't talk
cause she's in character!
Then she means yes?
No!
That terrifying glare that
makes your blood run cold!
The perfect Coulia impression!
It's almost a little too scary...
T-thank you so much!
Why is this happening to me?!
Nonoa-chan's doing photos now!
For real?! Let's go!
How long is this gonna take?! Come on!
At 1 PM, we'll have our Rock-Paper-Scissors
tournament at the main stage!
To prep for the tournament,
our photo areas will close at 12:30. Thank you!
Already?! That's in thirty minutes!
But I guess this event is about
more than just cosplay...
Look, there's Liliel!
We saw you on Mr. Camera's blog!
We're huge fans!
Huh?! T-thank you!
I have fans? I could cry!
But I have to go find Nonoa-chan!
Hey, could we get a picture of you?
We heard you were here and
have been looking all over for you!
There's only thirty minutes left!
I-I can't tell them no...
But if I let them take pictures,
I won't be able to catch Nonoa-chan...
Cinderella Stars
Liliel!
Nagomi-san?
It's really her!
Sorry, am I interrupting?
Uh, no, but...
Wait, both of them are here?
She posted a picture with her before.
I'm really sorry, but could I take pictures here?
GLARE
Nowhere else can handle my crowd.
Y-yeah, of course!
I'm so sorry to interrupt!
No, no, you're good!
I can't believe Nagomi-chan is talking to me.
You two can cut straight to the front of the line.
The front of the line...
...for a Heavenly Queen?!
Nagomi-san...
Go.
I'm sorry!
Wait, Liliel-chan!
I'm... Good with Nagomi-chan.
What?! Dude!
Why am I always like this?
I should just tell people how I feel.
We'd all be better off...
What am I supposed to do?
What can I do?
Nonoa-chan!
Liliel!
Both Rising Stars...
Liliel-chan?
Excuse me! Sorry! Really sorry!
Why?
Will you take pictures with me?!
They're both here!
Hell yeah!
Didn't Nonoa-chan just ghost her?
Why?
Did she?
After what I did to her...
She still...
Say something.
This time, I have to say something!
M-my voice worked fine before!
All I have to say is 'yes'!
I just have to nod!
But the thought of talking to someone
I like so much is terrifying...
Does she not like me?
Am I bothering her?
I'm being awkward.
She told me no before.
What matters is what you think.
Let's do this!
She might not like me,
but I want to believe that all cosplayers are allies,
are my friends!
No matter what you might think of me,
I still want to cosplay with you!
She's an angel...
Descending from heaven to take the stage, Liliel!
It's Liliel...
She's here, in real life!
Who am I, then?
Who's the girl standing next to her?
S...
Sparkling like transparent ice,
Cobalt Blue, the seventh Cinderella...
Coulia!
She spoke!
Nonoa-chan...
We're ready for pictures now!
The two most talked-about
cosplayers are here, together!
I can't believe they're at this event!
I'm so glad I came!
Next, let's do the pose from their Second Live!
That's Coulia's debut scene!
I love that part!
Ririsa...
Half an hour ago,
she was worried sick about Nonoa not liking her.
They grow up so fast.
Okay, I'm gonna snap some pics.
Hold my stuff.
Wait, I thought I was the photographer here!
We've only got ten minutes left!
I'm going in, too!
What's next?
That's the pose from the album art
for my song, Angels Up!
Even if I can't speak,
I can communicate with my love for the game,
with cosplay.
Thank you, Liliel-chan.
It feels like I've finally made a friend!
I'm so happy.
Look over here!
Thank you so much!
Sorry for dragging you into my shoot.
I just really wanted to get pictures with you.
I'm sorry...
Even now, I still can't speak.
I've gotta go. Thanks again.
Ririsa, you sure you don't want
to get her number or anything?
I would, but I've already bothered her enough.
I can't change how Nonoa-chan feels.
I told her how I feel,
and I don't want to keep pushing that on her.
I said my piece.
She's entitled to her own feelings about me.
Okay.
That's it, then.
Liliel-chan already has lots of friends.
She doesn't need me.
I got to live the dream for a moment.
That's enough for me.
But is it, though?
Didn't I come here to make friends with her?
That's right. This can't be it.
I'm not okay with things ending like this!
I can't make friends. I'm fine being alone.
Who was that?
Liliel-chan is a good person.
She was just being nice to me.
There's no way she'd actually
want to be friends with me.
Is that me?
Don't get excited just because
someone was nice to you.
I'll just end up bothering her.
I'll embarrass myself.
Shut up.
You're weird.
Stop it, shut up!
This is easier.
Stop!
When I speak,
I just end up making things worse.
When I try to involve myself with other people,
I just end up getting hurt.
Stop it, stop it!
Why are you saying this?!
Because everyone would be
better off if I didn't speak.
Right...
That's the person I turned myself into.
The person I became after years of overthinking.
I'll always be alone.
No one will ever want me.
I won't have friends.
I'll never be able to make friends.
I'll be alone forever.
Stop it. You're not me!
I'm Nonoa.
You're not!
You're the person I was,
until yesterday!
I won't stay the same.
I found the strength to speak.
I told someone how I feel.
I connected with someone I like!
So what?
I was Coulia.
I was just playing make-believe.
Who cares?!
I can become someone I'm not!
That means I can be someone different today!
A new me!
I can change.
I'm going to change!
Nonoa-chan?
Will...
Will you be my friend?
Yes! Of course I'll be your friend!
I can change.
I wonder if my past self would believe me...
Don't cry, Nonoa-chan!
...if I told her my first friend
would be the angel I loved so dearly.
That's great, Mikari-chan!
Turn a little to the side for me?
If I remember right,
That's it! Perfect!
Senpai was going to some event with everyone today.
If I don't do something soon, then...
Ooh, that serious expression is great!
C'mon, focus!
If my plan to win Senpai's heart by becoming
Yes, perfect!
a famous model didn't work out,
Now look at me!
then I'm just going to have to
go with the cosplay plan after all!
Okay, that's a wrap!
Thank you!
Could I borrow you for that interview now?
Sure!
I would, but...
Going straight to the CEO won't help.
Cosplay just wouldn't
work with our agency's strategy.
It's crazy to believe you were
once extremely shy, Mikari-chan.
I know, but once I've got
my mind set on something,
I just go after it, you know?
So I will.
What do you like to do on your days off?
I'll be strategic about this!
I love to cosplay!
Cosplay? Wow.
Yeah, I'm super into it!
I've been thinking about putting some of
my cosplay pics up on my social media!
When was she going to tell me this?!
Hope you're ready, Senpai!
I'll Keep Evolving